

PROFILE

Thanks for reviewing my resume! I am a 23-year-old recent college graduate looking for a career in software development. Although much of my background is in health services, through working with medical software and taking full-stack development courses I have truly found my passion in this area.

CONTACT

PHONE:

936-671-3228

WEBSITE:

https://github.com/ThatSkiPatroller

EMAIL:

t.suit@utexas.edu

HOBBIES

Skiing Music

TRACE SUITER

Full Stack Web Developer

EDUCATION

The University of Texas at Austin

2015 - 2021

Bachelor of Science and Arts in Biology

Hudson High School

2011 - 2015

CERTIFICATIONS

Outdoor Emergency Care Technician

2015 – Present (Renewed every year through coursework)

The Coding Bootcamp at The University of Texas at Austin 2020 - 2021

WORK EXPERIENCE

Rocky Mountain Division Ski Patroller at Ski Apache, NM

2015 – Present (seasonal)

Awards: National Ski Patrol's Rookie of the Year Award

Pineywood's Obstetrics and Gynecology

Office Assistant – as needed 2020 - Present

SKILLS

- ✓ HTML
- ✓ CSS
- ✓ Node.is
- ✓ React.js
- ✓ JavaScript
- √ iQuery
- ✓ Git Bash/ Github
- ✓ Teamwork